{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4640","name":"Little Caesar's #149","address":"15405 Gratiot Ave","zipcode":"48209","owner":"Little Caesar's Ent.","licenseNumber":"079469","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"5/12/2016","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","geom":"0101000020E610000020FC79BD15BE54C020349A4D61394540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43852","establishmentid":"4640","name":"Little Caesar's #149","inspectionDate":"2018-10-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"137","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"5","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"5","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43852","inspectionDate":"10/18/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4640","name":"Little Caesar's #149","violationCode":"4-602.12","violationDescription":"(A) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking and baking EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours. This section does not apply to hot oil cooking and filtering EQUIPMENT if it is cleaned as specified in Subparagraph 4-602.11(D)(6).   \r\n(B) The cavities and door seals of microwave ovens shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours by using the manufacturer's recommended cleaning procedure.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Baking and cooking equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as required above."},{"inspectionid":"43852","inspectionDate":"10/18/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4640","name":"Little Caesar's #149","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"43852","inspectionDate":"10/18/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4640","name":"Little Caesar's #149","violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored in soiled, wet conditions","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store in protected manner."},{"inspectionid":"43852","inspectionDate":"10/18/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4640","name":"Little Caesar's #149","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"43852","inspectionDate":"10/18/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4640","name":"Little Caesar's #149","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"43852","inspectionDate":"10/18/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4640","name":"Little Caesar's #149","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Replace."}]},{"inspectionid":"40083","establishmentid":"4640","name":"Little Caesar's #149","inspectionDate":"2017-09-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"1","pfcount":"1","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40083","inspectionDate":"9/21/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4640","name":"Little Caesar's #149","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"TOP LOADER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"inspectionid":"40083","inspectionDate":"9/21/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4640","name":"Little Caesar's #149","violationCode":"4-901.11","violationDescription":"After cleaning and SANITIZING, EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS shall be air-dried or used after adequate draining.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Clean equipment and utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored/stacked wet","subProblem":"","location":"EQUIPMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Completely air dry all items prior to storage/use."},{"inspectionid":"40083","inspectionDate":"9/21/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4640","name":"Little Caesar's #149","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Replace."}]},{"inspectionid":"36311","establishmentid":"4640","name":"Little Caesar's #149","inspectionDate":"2016-08-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36311","inspectionDate":"8/23/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4640","name":"Little Caesar's #149","violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"36311","inspectionDate":"8/23/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4640","name":"Little Caesar's #149","violationCode":"3-302.12","violationDescription":"Except for containers holding FOOD that can be readily and unmistakably recognized such as dry pasta, working containers holding FOOD or FOOD ingredients that are removed from their original packages for use in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, such as cooking oils, flour, herbs, potato flakes, salt, spices, and sugar shall be identified with the common name of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not identified","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4640"}}